<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>Puss in boots - Jekyll Bootstrap</title>
        <description>Puss in boots - Jekyll Bootstrap - Jobe Roberts</description>
        <link>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots/</link>
        <link>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots/</link>
        <lastBuildDate>2014-05-11T20:41:25-04:00</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>2014-05-11T20:41:25-04:00</pubDate>
        <ttl>1800</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>More About The Bar B Q</title>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;as_you_may_know_i_was_going_to_ditch_my_old_barbq&quot;&gt;As you may know, I was going to ditch my old bar-b-q.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The neighbour down the street rolled it away. Hopefully it all works out for him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’m thinking I like living without a Bar B Q. Just continue using the stove.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those of you in favour of getting a new Bar B Q let me know why I should.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;china_super_smog&quot;&gt;China Super Smog&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here in Gatineau we have beautiful weather and blue skies. We are so fortunate. I cannot imagine living in cities with so much smog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s so thick you can barely see through it. You know we’re all connected on this spaceship earth. Burning coal is unecessary when you could be burning Thorium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Converting coal into a clean energy source is possible, but why when safe nuclear is possible and cheaper?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                <link>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//reuse/2014/05/11/more-about-the-bar-b-q</link>
                <guid>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//reuse/2014/05/11/more-about-the-bar-b-q</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-05-11T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Wordcamp Ottawa 2014</title>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;wordcamp_ottawa_started_off_with_a_zurb&quot;&gt;WordCamp Ottawa started off with a ZURB&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaker Brendan Sera-Shriar of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thebrendans.com/&quot;&gt;theBrendans&lt;/a&gt; was pretty funny and very relaxed. His talk aimed to convince us to use the Zurb Foundation framework which uses SASS, font icons, and zepto.js&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It all sounded quite impressive and it seems well worth the effort to first design for the little mobile interface and then scale up to your 50” TVs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This code began from a mobile app perspective but it also produces excellent responsive web pages you can put on your WordPress site. I’ll have to give it a try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots/images/wordpress-pin.jpg' /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;false_floors_and_cake_layers&quot;&gt;False floors and cake layers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New jargon to learn about. Do you know where to find the hamburger icon? Do you use it very often?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were just so many wonderful presentations to see, 32 in all on Saturday, fortunately WordCamp continues again tomorrow at noon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to more great stuff.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                <link>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//events/2014/05/03/WordCamp-Ottawa-2014</link>
                <guid>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//events/2014/05/03/WordCamp-Ottawa-2014</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-05-03T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Old Bar B Q</title>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;im_going_to_ditch_my_old_barbq&quot;&gt;I’m going to ditch my old bar-b-q.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It still works, but it’s getting pretty rusted inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to judge these things; probably when there are flames shooting out the bottom it’s time to stop using your old bar-b-q.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to push it out front and put a ‘free’ sign on it. Somebody will no doubt pick it up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;peak_metal&quot;&gt;Peak metal&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re going to be digging up less and less metal because there’s less of it to dig up. Not sure how recycling factors in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Makes me wonder if I should recycle my bar-b-q, lots of shiny metal still left in her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;scrap_for_cash&quot;&gt;Scrap for cash&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My buddy Mitch tells me you can get cash for scrap metal. Of course, the heavier the metal the better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                <link>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//reuse/2014/04/28/old-bar-b-q</link>
                <guid>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//reuse/2014/04/28/old-bar-b-q</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-04-28T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Oculus Less Than Evil Vr</title>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;oculus_vr_was_recently_purchased_by_facebook_for_2_billion&quot;&gt;Oculus VR was recently purchased by Facebook for $2 billion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other night, I was privileged to have had the opportunity to try out the new &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.oculusvr.com/&quot;&gt;Oculus Rift&lt;/a&gt; devkit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was surprising just how much you actually feel like you're in this virtual space, as you pan around the graphics match exactly what you'd see in the virtual space. Er.. you really have to try it to see what I mean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lots of fun, I haven’t tried anything like that before. I kept trying to touch things that were in front of me. It was weird not to see your own hands though. As I understand someone is working on gloves to interface with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;blockabout&quot;&gt;Blockabout&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blockabout was a surprisingly fun game that I got to try out with the goggles on. To my delight I even got to experience getting eaten alive by pirahnas, nasty little fish! &amp;gt;&amp;lt;}}}•&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The physics in this game is playful yet realistic at the same time. This game is expected to be released in the coming weeks. You will be able to download for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check it out here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://blockabout.ca/index.php?Lang=En&amp;ID=1&quot;&gt;Blockabout&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the_star_trek_holodeck&quot;&gt;the Star Trek holodeck&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you're viewing the virtual Star Trek enterprise via your VR goggles go to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Holodeck&quot;&gt;holodeck&lt;/a&gt; to experience virtual reality within a virtual reality game. Mind blowing! &lt;img src=&quot;http://emoticons4u.com/happy/010.gif&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;warning_may_experience_dizziness&quot;&gt;warning: may experience dizziness.&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
                <link>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//virtual%20reality/2014/04/11/oculus-less-than-evil-vr</link>
                <guid>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//virtual%20reality/2014/04/11/oculus-less-than-evil-vr</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-04-11T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Lock Down Extremola</title>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;extreme_lockdown_mode&quot;&gt;Extreme lock-down mode!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;computer_says_no&quot;&gt;Computer says NO.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forget trying to run Jekyll on your government issued pc, no, no, no, this machine has been locked down and preventive measures are now taken for such nonsense. Jekyll, spuhfah! not here. It's for my own safety no doubt. So for now, I can only get this running from my offsite mac.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can give it a try yourself if you don't want to take my word for it (typically a wise choice not to). Perhaps you'll be able to install ruby, and even python, but run Jekyll and this will cause you grief. I tell you, NOT!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;im_not_complaining_god_no&quot;&gt;I’m not complaining, God no&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, yes probably, there's just so much you can't do from within the firewall, so don't even try it buster. :-(&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which also reminds me that everything that is written here will go down on my permanent record or until I delete it. Of course, anyone at anytime can clone/copy/fork or so otherwise copy this site in its entirety with a click of a button. Uh but isn’t that the norm now? Copy/Paste. Copy/Paste. Feel the power! Savour it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;physical_space_coordinates&quot;&gt;Physical Space Coordinates&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt='Kent and Laurier' src='https://farm4.staticflickr.com/3139/3097094692_b6e087a5a8_n.jpg' /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Kent and Laurier” photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/joberrr/&quot;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                <link>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//lock-down/2014/04/08/lock-down-extremola</link>
                <guid>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//lock-down/2014/04/08/lock-down-extremola</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-04-08T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>About This Site</title>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;who_runs_this_show&quot;&gt;Who runs this show?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Jobe Roberts and I work for the Government of Canada in the Department of Fisheries and Oceans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll is new to me, I tend to use WordPress most often. Getting better at Git.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also find me on twitter: &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/joberrr&quot;&gt;@joberrr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;dont_like_what_you_see_have_suggestions&quot;&gt;Don’t like what you see? Have suggestions?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, don’t hesitate, tell me what you want me to know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;thats_all_folks&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;That’s all folks!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;</description>
                <link>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//about/2014/04/07/about-this-site</link>
                <guid>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//about/2014/04/07/about-this-site</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-04-07T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>You Are Not Your User</title>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;i_design_this_site_for_my_own_selfish_reasons&quot;&gt;I design this site for my own selfish reasons&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether it be writing code or writing a web program it has been suggested that it’s useful to have an audience or user in mind. Right now that user is mostly me. I know, this is a design faux-pas. &lt;a href=&quot;http://52weeksofux.com/post/385981879/you-are-not-your-user&quot;&gt;You are not your user&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But seriously, this site is aimed at pleasing me mostly. So there you have it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;goals&quot;&gt;Goals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d love to manage to get simplenote.js running on this site. That’d be cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Activate Disqus&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just have to find the right line in the “_config.yml” I think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did that work?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
                <link>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//about/2014/04/04/you-are-not-your-user</link>
                <guid>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//about/2014/04/04/you-are-not-your-user</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Photo Of My Cat Bubba</title>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;my_cat_sometimes_barks&quot;&gt;My cat sometimes barks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He used to bark a lot when he was a kitten. Now that only happens when you pet his belly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://farm1.staticflickr.com/124/347940223_29fe195936_q.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bubba my cat&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                <link>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//photo/2014/04/04/photo-of-my-cat-bubba</link>
                <guid>http://joberrr.github.io/puss-in-boots//photo/2014/04/04/photo-of-my-cat-bubba</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
